3dscanstore.com 2018-10-02

# Privacy Policy

1\. Personal Information We Collect

We collect certain personal information about visitors and users of our service.  

1.1. Personal Information.  
  
The most common types of information we collect without user registration are IP addresses and web analytics data. If a user registers an account with 3D scan store we require them to submit first name, last name, email address, and physical address. In the case of a transaction on 3D scan store  we do not collect your credit / debit card numbers, all sensitive payment information is handled by PayPal  

1.2. Sensitive Personal Information.

We do not collect any sensitive personal information.

1.3. Cookies and web analytics.

When you visit 3D Scan Store, there’s certain information that’s recorded which is generally anonymous information and does not reveal your identity.

Like many websites, when you visit 3D Scan Store, in order to deliver a full browsing experience a small amount of information, known as a ‘cookie’ will be downloaded to your device, (e.g.: your computer, laptop, tablet or mobile phone). A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website but these cookies cannot be used to identify you personally. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

These cookies are used to improve your browsing experience by, for example:

– Enabling a website to recognise your device so you do not have to give the same information several times during one task or browsing sessions;

– Recognising if you have given a username and password so you do not need to do it for every web page you visit;

– Analysing anonymous data to help us understand how visitors interact with the website so we can make improvements and develop the website in an informed way for our visitors.

We will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. If you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by our website, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your web browser settings.

The ‘Help’ function within your browser should tell you how to do this. Alternatively, you may wish to visit

http://www.aboutcookies.org. This website contains detailed information on how to manage cookies across a wide variety of browsers. You will also find details on how to delete cookies from your device, as well as more general information about cookies. Please be aware that restricting cookies may have an impact on the functionality of our website.

When visiting 3D Scan Store, in addition to cookies, the following kinds of details may also be captured:  

  * Your IP address or proxy server IP address’;

  * The domain name you requested;

  * The name of your internet service provider is sometimes captured depending on the configuration of your ISP connection;

  * The date and time of your visit to the website;

  * The length of your session;

  * The pages which you have accessed;

  * The number of times you access our site within any month;

  * The file URL you look at and information relating to it;

  * The website which referred you to our Service; and

  * The operating system which your computer uses.

2\. How We Collect Personal Information

We collect personal information directly when you provide it to us, automatically as you use our Service.

 **2.1. User-submitted Information.**

We collect your personal information when you provide it to us when you complete membership registration and buy items or services on 3D Scan Store, subscribe to a newsletter, email list, submit feedback, enter a contest, fill out a survey, or send us a communication.

 **2.2. The personal information we collect about you from others.** Although we generally collect personal information directly from you, on occasion, we also   

**a.** Transaction details from our trusted payment providers in order to process a transaction;

 **b.** third party service providers (like Google, Facebook, Dropbox) which may provide information about you when you link, connect, or log in to your account with the third party provider and they send us information usually limited to your name and email; and

 **c.** other third-party sources/ and or partners whereby we receive additional information about you (to the extent permitted by applicable law), such as demographic data or fraud detection information, and combine it with information we have about you. For example, fraud warnings from service providers like identity verification service.   

3\. How We Use Your Personal Information  

**3.1. To fulfill a contract, or take steps linked to a contract.** In particular, in facilitating and processing transactions that take place on 3D Scan Store, like when you purchase an item.  

**3.2. When necessary for purposes in our legitimate interest.** These interests include:  

**a.**  Operating the Service;  

**b.**  Providing you with services described on 3D Scan Store  

**c.**  Verifying your identity when you sign in to 3D Scan Store  

**d.**  Responding to support emails, and helping facilitate the resolution of any disputes;  

**e.**  Updating you with operational news and information about our Service e.g. to notify you about changes to Service, website disruptions or security updates  

**f.**  Carrying out technical analysis to determine how to improve the Service we provide  

**g.**  Monitoring activity on 3D Scan Store, e.g. to identify potentially fraudulent activity and to ensure compliance with the user terms that apply to the Service;  

**h.**  Managing our relationship with you, e.g. by responding to your comments or queries submitted to us on the Service or asking for your feedback or whether you want to participate in a survey;  

**i.**  Managing our legal and operational affairs (including, managing risks relating to content and fraud matters);  

**g.**  Training 3D Scan Store staff about how to best serve our user community  

**k.**  Improving our products and services.  

**l.**  Providing general administrative and perform functions and activities;  

**3.3. When you give us consent.  
**  
To provide a better experience and bring you more value, we will use your personal information to:  

**a.**  Provide you with marketing information about products and services which we feel may interest you  

**b.**  Customize our services and websites, such as advertising that may appear on 3D Scan Store – where this involves the use of cookies or similar technologies – in order to provide a more personalised experience.  

4\. How We Share Your Information  

**4.1. Selling Personal Information.  
**  
We will not rent or sell your personal information to others under any circumstances.  

**4.2. When absolutely necessary we may disclose personal information to the following recipients** :  

  * Authors of any items or services made available to you so they can facilitate support;  

  * Our professional advisers (lawyers, accountants, financial advisers etc.);  

  * Regulators and government authorities in connection with our compliance procedures and obligations;  

  * Purchaser or prospective purchaser of all or part of our assets or our business, and their professional advisers;  

  * In connection with the purchase;

  * Third party to respond to requests relating to a criminal investigation or alleged or suspected illegal activity;  

  * Third party, in order to enforce or defend our rights, or to address financial or reputational risks;  

  * Rights holder in relation to an allegation of intellectual property infringement or any other infringement; and
  * Other recipients where we are authorised or required by law to do so.  

5\. How We Protect Your Information  

We store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us and our service providers. Personal information that we store or transmit is protected by security and access controls, including username and password authentication, two-factor authentication, and data encryption where appropriate.  

6\. How you can access your personal information  

You can access some of the personal information that we collect about you by logging in to your account. You also have the right to make a request to access other personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. You can also close the account you have with us at any time. To make an access or correction request, contact us directly at info@3dscansrtore.com  

7\. How long we keep your personal information  

We retain your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide the Service to you and others, and to comply with our legal obligations. If you no longer want us to use your personal information or to provide you with the 3D Scan Store services, you can request that we erase your personal information and close your 3D Scan Store account. Please note that if you request the erasure of your personal information we will retain information from deleted accounts as necessary for our legitimate business interests, to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect fees, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, enforce the terms of service and take other actions permitted by law. The information we retain will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  

8\. Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Members. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on 3D Scan Store. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@3dscanstore.com

9.Your Choices & Rights

Your choices

Where you have given us your consent, you can withdraw it by doing the following.

  * To stop receiving our marketing you can change your preferences within your account, follow the unsubscribe instructions in any of the emails we send you or contact us and we will do it for you.

Your rights

You also have rights over how your personal information is used including:

  * The right to object to our processing of your data.

  * The right to request that your information be erased or restricted from further use.

  * The right to request a copy of the information we hold about you.

  * The right to correct, amend or update the information you have given us (where you have an account with us you can also do this by logging in and updating your information)

To make changes to your account and personal information please [login here ](http://www.3dscanstore.com/index.php?route=account/login)  

3D scan store respects the privacy of the personal information of the individuals with whom we interact. 3D scan store does not disclose personal information of our members or those individuals who visit our website. No newsletters or offers will be sent to you without your prior consent. Any information submitted by the buyer will be used solely for the purpose of completing the transaction, delivering the product and addressing any customer service issues.

**We do not store credit card** **details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties**
